# **RESUME**

## SHAILESH N.BHATT (DMLT)

### Experience of working in Laboratory over 10 years

Address: Sun Real Homes, New Ranip,

Ahmedabad

Contact No.: 8511991287

#### **JOB OBJECTIVE:**

Skilled Medical Laboratory Technologist with over 10 years of experience seeking Position as a Lab. Technician. Good analytical and fast learner with proven ability to manage and execute in all facets of a busy medical laboratories.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

#### **B.A.P.S HOSPITAL** (Shahibuag)

Ahmedabad, India.

Continue from December 2015

#### **Designation:**

Laboratory Technician

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Phlebotomy
- Handling and analysis of Biological samples
- Performed Serological, Hematology, Biochemical & all other tests.
- To plan and implement Internal Quality control process in the laboratory.
- Perform daily, weekly & periodic maintenance, calibration & OC check for all analyzer.
- Inventory management.
- Laboratory documentation Work (SOPs) & Coordination

## KRISHNA SHALBY HOSPITAL ( BOPAL)

#### **NABL Accredited Lab**

Ahmedabad, India

17 Feb 2015 to Dec 2015

#### **Designation:**

Laboratory Technician

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Actively participate in SOP writing and review.
- Train junior staff as a part of on-job training.
- Ensure Quality of examination results.
- Perform Daily QC, troubleshoot as & when required.
- Analyze the patient samples as per respective SOPs and validate results.

#### S.A.L SCIENTIFIC AND DIAGNOSTIC CENTER

#### NABL Accredited Lab, Ahmedabad

## **Designation:**

Medical Laboratory Assistant/Phlebotomist

Jan 2012 to Jan 2015

Jan 2005 to Dec 2009

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Phlebotomy
- Perform Daily QC, troubleshoot as & when required.
- Analyze the patient samples and validate results.
- Reporting of results to Consultants and communication to Medical Officer
- To maintain all Laboratory documents.
- Supportive for NABL work and helpful for documentation.
- Very good skill for Phlebotomy specially pediatric collection and arterial blood collection.

### • NOON FOOD LTD.(UK)

**LONDON** 

#### **Designation:**

**Quality Controller** 

Dec 2009 to Dec 2011.

#### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION**:

D.M.L.T( Diploma In Medical Laboratory Technician)
Gujarat Institute of Technology AHMEDABAD

### **OPERATING INSTRUMENTS:**

- COBAS400 PLUSE (ROACH)
- COBAS e411 (ROACH)
- VITROS 350
- MINI VIDAS
- SYSMAX I8OOi 5PART FULLY AUTOMATED HEMATOLOGY ANALYSER
- MINDRAY BC5380 5 PART FULLY AUTOMATED HEMATOLOGY ANALYSER
- STAGO I state
- ACL ALERE FOR COAGULATION STUDY
- CA-50
- COBAS b 121
- ABOTT I state
- CHEM7 SEMI BIO CHEMISTRY ANALYSER.
- EC5
- Backman coulter
- Au 480 for bio chemistry.
- Blood cross matching and Routin Micro work.

## **PERSONAL DETAILS:**

• NAME: SHAILESH.N.BHATT

 ADDRESS: A-202,PART-2 SUNREAL HOMES, NR.GST CROSSING,NEW RANIP, AHMEDABAD – 382480

• MOB|LE NO: 8511991287

• DATE OF BIRTH: 21/05/1987

• LANGUAGES: ENGLISH, HINDI, GUJARATI

• HOBBY: MUSIC, READING AND TRAVELLING

• E-MAIL ADDRESS: <a href="mailto:shail\_bhatt2009@yahoo.com">shail\_bhatt2009@yahoo.com</a>

Your's faithfully

(Shailesh.Bhatt)